When you want to use a database in your application,
如果你想在应用程序上 使用数据库
first you need to create the database and give it a name.
则你首先需要 创建一个数据库并命名
You'll use the create database thread for this.
为此你将用到 create database 命令
The name you give it here,
你将在此处提供的名称
is the same name you'll use to connect to the database from your code.
与将用来从代码 连接数据库所用的名称相同
The opposite of create in SQL is drop.
与在 SQL 中 create 命令 相对的是 drop 命令
I'm not sure why.
我不清楚原因
Maybe database programmers used to be really clumsy.
可能是因为数据库程序员 以前都比较笨拙
Anyway, the way to remove a data base, is drop database.
不管怎样 删除数据库的方法 是使用 drop database 命令
And the way to remove a table is drop table.
删除表格的方法 是使用 drop table 命令
All of these commands have options,
所有这些命令都有 options
you can look up in the documentation if you ever need them.
如有需要你可以查看文档
When you drop a data base or
当你删除数据库或表格时
a table, there's no confirmation, no did you really mean to do that warning.
没有确认信息 不会出现 “你确定要这么做吗？”的警告
So don't do it, if you don't really mean it.
所以 如果你不打算删除  请不要这么做
Once you've created a database in psql, you'll want to connect to it.
在 psql 中创建数据库后  你需要连接该数据库
You can do that using the backslash C command,
你可以使用 \C 后面跟 数据库名称的命令
followed by the database's name.
来连接
By the way, you can't drop a database that you're connected to.
另外 你无法删除 已连接的数据库
Try these commands on your own in your VM using psql.
你可以使用 psql 在自己的 VM 上试一下这些命令
First, create a new database called fishies, or whatever you'd like.
首先 创建一个数据库 命名为 fishies 或其他你喜欢的名称
Once you've created it,
创建该数据库后
switch psql's connection over to that database, with \c fishies.
当使用的是 psql 时 会使用 \c fishies 命令 连接该数据库
Then create a table, make one of the columns a text column,
然后创建一个表格  其中有一列为 text 列
one of the columns a serial column.
一列为 serial 列
Then try inserting some values with the text column and
然后尝试插入一些值到 text 列
selecting some rows from the table.
并从表格中选择(select)一些行
What do you think will happen in the serial column,
如果你插入的行不能提供值
when you insert a row that doesn't give it a value?
则你认为 serial 列会出现什么情况？
Try it in psql.
在 psql 中尝试一下
What was it that actually happened?
看看到底会发生什么
Then after that,
之后
try finding a description of this behavior in the post SQL documentation.
尝试在 PostSQL 文档 中说明此行为